<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pelis</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world! This six hour Classical Music arrangement features some of the best piano Sonatas by Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart , the famous Austrian composer and pianist.

It\'s the perfect playlist for studying, relaxing, homework, video gaming, sleeping, babies, deep relaxation and mediation and some use it as elevator or hotel lobby and lounge music!
Long music for meditation and relaxation.
Zen music for meditation, Guided Meditation.
Meditation Music, Soothing Music, Calming Music, Relax Piano Music.

Description in other languages:

Мeditation, relaxation, sleep music, music to sleep, music to study, guided meditation, relaxation music, spiritual music, music for studying, music for learning, background music, music for meditation, music to relax, instrumental music, music for homework, yoga music, ambient music, relaxdaily, chillout, slow music, piano music, soothing music, new age music, peaceful music, beautiful music, de-stress music, sleep musiс, relaxing music, zen music, massage music, spa music, soft music, slow music, music anti-stress, healing music, wellness music, piano music, mood music, youtube music, relax music playlist, tranquil music, slow instrumental, peaceful music, slow background music, wonderful music, chill study music, new age music playlist, ambient music for studying, peaceful background music, soothing background music, baby music, soothing music, musica zen, background music instrumental, slow instrumental music.
mood music instrumental.

расслабляющая музыка, музыка для релаксации, музыка для сна, музыка для медитации, спокойная музыка, музыка для засыпания, музыка для йоги, медитация, йога,звуки природы.

Relaxing Piano Music --- http://youtu.be/g54-_icmfo4

Entspannungsmusik, entspannungsmusik zum einschlafen, entspannungsmusik klavier, schlafen, yoga, entspannungsklänge, Musik für Meditation, Instrumentalmusik, Musik zu studieren, Meditation.

Musique de méditation, détendez musique, du sommeil, de la musique pour dormir, musique à étudier, la musique de dormir, la musique de fond, la musique instrumentale, le yoga, la méditation, tibétain Healing Sounds, sons de la nature, le soulagement du stress.
    </string>
    <string name="bye_world">Chau loco!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
</resources>
